let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is the largest continent in the World ?",
    answer: "Asia",
    options: [
      "Africa",
      "Europe",
      "Asia",
      "North America"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which continent is known as cold desert ?",
    answer: "Antarctica",
    options: [
      "Europe",
      "South America",
      "Africa",
      "Antarctica"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which continent has only one country ?",
    answer: "Australia",
    options: [
      "Europe",
      "Australia",
      "Antarctica",
      "North America"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which continent covers about 20 percent of the total landmass on planet Earth ?",
    answer: "Africa",
    options: [
      "Africa",
      "North America",
      "Asia",
      "South America"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which continent has both the highest and the lowest points on Earth ?",
    answer: "Asia",
    options: [
      "Asia",
      "North America",
      "Antarctica",
      "Europe"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "In which Continent is Amazon Rainforest situated?",
    answer: "South America",
    options: [
      "South America",
      "North America",
      "Africa",
      "Asia"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which is the smallest continent in area?",
    answer: "Australia",
    options: [
      "Europe",
      "North America",
      "Australia",
      "Antarctica"
    ]
  },

  
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which continent has largest number of countries?",
    answer: "Africa",
    options: [
      "Africa",
      "North America",
      "Asia",
      "South America"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The longest river in the world, Nile is situated in which continent?",
    answer: "Africa",
    options: [
      "Africa",
      "North America",
      "Asia",
      "South America"
    ]
  },

  
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which continent is also called Dark Continent? ",
    answer: "Africa",
    options: [
      "Asia",
      "North America",
      "Africa",
      "South America"
    ]
  },
  
];